Pride Center of the Capital Region; Records apap361
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Pride Center of the Capital Region Records
1972 - 2017 April 7
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap361
25 cubic ft.
149 captures
This collection contains records documenting the day-to-day activities of the Pride Center of the Capital Region.
Collection X
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Biographical History
Founded in 1970 in Albany New York, the Pride Center of the Capital Region promotes the well-being of all lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and queer-identified people as well as those affected by discrimination based on their gender identity and expression. Its programs held both at the Center, and throughout the region, help advocate for members of the LGTBQ community, educate people on LGTBQ issues and promote awarness and pride. As the oldest continuously-operating LGBTQ community center in the country, the Pride Center has worked to build a welcoming and empowering community for all people.
The Pride Center formed in 1970 under the name of the Gay Liberation Front. It was renamed the Capital District Gay Community Council in 1972 and later was the Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council before becoming the Pride Center in 2011.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of newsletters written by the center, other publications about the LGBTQ community, administrative files, records from Capital Pride and other events held by the center, and subject files relating to other LGBTQ events and organizations.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged alphabetically except for the Community news publications which are arranged chronologically.
Acquisition Information
The Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, Inc. donated initial materials (predmoinantly publications) to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2005. In 2016, the Pride Center donated a much larger amount of records. Lawrence Van Heusen donated a small number of additional items in 2017.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted. Some folders in the Administrative Files and Events series are restricted due to personal information. Consult a staff member for further details.
Web Archives; Community organization--New York (State)--Albany; Gay activists -- New York (State).; Lesbian activists -- New York (State).; Transgender people--New York (State); Albany (N.Y.) Politics and government--20th century; Pride Center of the Capital Region
- Pride Center of the Capital Region Website, 2011 February 3 - 2017 April 7; 1; 149 captures
  URL
  https://www.capitalpridecenter.org/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: Pride Center of the Capital Region
  created_date: 2016-08-25T19:14:00Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:39:07Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
    crawl: 232508
    This item had no crawl rules.
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-08-25T19:20:44Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-25T19:20:44Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-28T19:50:53Z
    end_date: 2016-08-28T19:36:13Z
    elapsed_ms: 260114881
    Crawl Types
    type: TEST_SAVED
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: True
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 259200
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 241065
    novel_count: 62389
    duplicate_count: 1396
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 177280
    downloaded_count: 63785
    download_failures: 2
    warc_revisit_count: 1395
    warc_url_count: 63778
    total_data_in_kbs: 3391265
    duplicate_bytes: 51645407
    warc_compressed_bytes: 182402841
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.25
    kb_rate: 13.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
    crawl: 241073
    Crawl Rules
    Limit host facebook.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twimg.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twitter.com to 500 documents
    start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:51Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:51Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-10T21:16:59Z
    end_date: 2016-10-10T20:41:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 260595260
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    test: False
    discovered_count: 242376
    novel_count: 60987
    duplicate_count: 3589
    queued_count: 177800
    downloaded_count: 64576
    warc_revisit_count: 3588
    warc_url_count: 64569
    total_data_in_kbs: 3422578
    duplicate_bytes: 447835716
    warc_compressed_bytes: 811705156
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
    crawl: 247622
    start_date: 2016-11-07T20:17:54Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-07T20:17:54Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-10T20:34:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-10T20:19:34Z
    elapsed_ms: 259295153
    discovered_count: 239435
    novel_count: 60745
    duplicate_count: 6469
    queued_count: 172221
    downloaded_count: 67214
    warc_revisit_count: 6469
    warc_url_count: 67207
    total_data_in_kbs: 3427608
    duplicate_bytes: 461867411
    warc_compressed_bytes: 794115439
    doc_rate: 0.26
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - 403 Forbidden, 2016 December 7
    crawl: 253244
    start_date: 2016-12-07T20:27:15Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-07T20:27:15Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-07T22:00:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-07T21:43:32Z
    elapsed_ms: 4509172
    status: FINISHED
    discovered_count: 1113
    novel_count: 1068
    duplicate_count: 45
    queued_count: 0
    downloaded_count: 1113
    download_failures: 0
    warc_revisit_count: 44
    warc_url_count: 1106
    total_data_in_kbs: 108315
    duplicate_bytes: 346437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22687529
    kb_rate: 24.0
  - WARC file for 403 Forbidden, 2016 December 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 January 7
    crawl: 258889
    start_date: 2017-01-07T20:17:35Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-07T20:17:35Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-07T20:54:19Z
    end_date: 2017-01-07T20:40:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 1380120
    discovered_count: 1867
    novel_count: 1392
    duplicate_count: 475
    downloaded_count: 1867
    warc_revisit_count: 475
    warc_url_count: 1860
    total_data_in_kbs: 129910
    duplicate_bytes: 29860738
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22061868
    doc_rate: 1.35
    kb_rate: 94.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 January 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 March 7
    crawl: 271771
    start_date: 2017-03-07T20:18:06Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-07T20:18:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-07T21:07:40Z
    end_date: 2017-03-07T20:57:41Z
    elapsed_ms: 2359321
    discovered_count: 1772
    novel_count: 968
    duplicate_count: 802
    queued_count: 2
    downloaded_count: 1770
    download_failures: 1
    warc_revisit_count: 801
    warc_url_count: 1763
    total_data_in_kbs: 127776
    duplicate_bytes: 35834352
    warc_compressed_bytes: 20002966
    doc_rate: 0.75
    kb_rate: 54.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 March 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 April 7
    crawl: 289349
    start_date: 2017-04-07T20:18:22Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-07T20:18:22Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-07T20:44:25Z
    end_date: 2017-04-07T20:34:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 937358
    discovered_count: 2013
    novel_count: 1072
    duplicate_count: 941
    downloaded_count: 2013
    warc_revisit_count: 939
    warc_url_count: 2006
    total_data_in_kbs: 137179
    duplicate_bytes: 35965743
    warc_compressed_bytes: 20559031
    doc_rate: 2.15
    kb_rate: 146.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 April 7
- Publications, 1973-2013; 5.8 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  The first sub-series of Community newsletters is arranged chronologically. The second sub-series of other publications is arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains newsletters created by the Pride Center. The newsletter called Community, updated members of the center of the upcoming activities of the center. The newsletters also include articles written by the members and announcements about any changes or updates to the center. This series also includes other publications written by other organizations and institutions about the LGBTQ community.
  - Community, 1973-2010; 2 cubic ft.
    This series is arranged chronologically.
    This sub-series contains the Community newsletter that the Pride Center published. The newsletter updated the members of the center on the events that were happening, as well as any updates or changes that were made. The newsletter also included stories written by members of the center. Due to limited funds, the newsletter was often cut short or not printed at all, so some years or months are missing from the collection.
    - Community, 1972; 1974; 1976-1989 (Oversize 1)
    - Community, 1990-1995 (Oversize 2)
    - Community, 1996-1999 (Oversize 3)
    - Community, 2000-2003 (Oversize 4)
    - Community, 2004-2007; 2009-2011 (Oversize 5)
  - Other Publications, 1973-2011; 3.8 cubic ft.
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically.
    This sub0-series contains publications related to the LGBTQ community. The centers community room was often filled with literature on the LGBTQ community so members could be informed and up-to-date on any issues and events. These other publications include run of The Advocate and The Gayzette.
    - 5th Freedom, 1978 (Oversize 6, Folder 1)
    - Advocate (1 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Advocate (2 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Advocate (3 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Advocate (4 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Advocate (5 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Advocate (6 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Advocate (7 of 7), 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Alive (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Alive (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Alive, 1982 (Oversize 6, Folder 2)
    - Art and Understanding, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Alyson: Gay Men's Book Catalog, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Amethyst, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Bidde, 1978 (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Body Positive, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Carillon, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Center Post, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 4)
    - Christopher Street (1 of 5), 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Christopher Street (2 of 5), 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Christopher Street (3 of 5), 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Christopher Street (4 of 5), 1987-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Christopher Street (5 of 5), 1987-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Civil Liberties, 1981 (Oversize 6, Folder 5)
    - the Connection, 1983 (Oversize 6, Folder 6)
    - E Squire, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Empty Closet, 1977 (Oversize 6, Folder 7)
    - Gay Light, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Gay People's Chronicle, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 8)
    - Gay Teachers Association Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Gay Report, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Gays on the Hill, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Gay Christian, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Gayzette, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Guide, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - High Gear- Ohio Gay Journal, 1978 (Oversize 6, Folder 9)
    - Hudson Mohawk, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - In Unity, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Inquiry, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - International Male, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - It's Time, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - It's Time News Letter of the Gay Task Force, 1979-1980 (Oversize 6, Folder 10)
    - Knickerbocker New, 1975 (Oversize 6, Folder 11)
    - Lambda Rising News, 1990 (Oversize 6, Folder 12)
    - Lambda Update, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Metro land, 1991 (Oversize 6, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter of the Capital District Gay Community Council, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Newsweek, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - New York Native, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - New York Native, 1989 (Oversize 6, Folder 14)
    - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Northview, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Oneonta Gayzette, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Out in the Mountains, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 15)
    - Pan, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - People For the American Way, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 16)
    - Pink Paper, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - POZ, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Produce Report, 1990-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Q News, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 17)
    - Recorder, 1997 (Oversize 6, Folder 18)
    - Sisters United, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Speak out, 1973-1974; 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - The Evening Bulletin, 1975 (Oversize 6, Folder 19)
    - This Week in Texas, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Triangle, 1996 (Oversize 6, Folder 20)
    - Transgenderist, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Up Front, 1979 (Oversize 6, Folder 21)
    - Yellow Star and the Pink Triangle, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Administrative Files, 1973-2015; 2.2 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains the administrative files of the Pride Center. Included in the records are bylaws, staff records, finanical records, membership papers and other administrative documents related to the day to day activities of the center. Some folders are restricted for due to personal information of staff and members of the center. Please consult an archivist before use.
  - Accessibility, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adoption of Community Council, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bank of America, United Way Campaign Donors - RESTRICTED, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult an archivist before viewing this material.
  - Anonymous Contingent Donation-First Floor Parlor, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Basement Repair, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bi Brunch Concem, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board Member Questionnaire Response, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors - RESTRICTED, 1999; 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Handbook, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Interests, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Resumes - RESTRICTED, 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board Orientation Manual, 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 2006; 2008 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board Reigration, 1990; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Build a Better Board -Participant Work Book, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Building Renovation Fund, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Building Use Contract, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bylaws, 1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Calendar, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Candidate Proposals, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Capital District Arts Decentralization Panel Grants, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carrie Kneep-Administrative Coordinator, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Causes Instructions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Center Use Sheet, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Certification Regarding Debarment, Suspension, and Other Responsibility Matters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clean Streak-Cleaning Services, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Communications Policy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Community Center Staffing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Community Room-A Place to Meet Friends, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Community-General Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Concerns Directed to Administration, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Continued Funding Application (CFA) For Health and Human Services for Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Individuals, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Copy Manifest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975; 1977-1981; 1998; 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Daily Schedule of Events, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Donations - RESTRICTED, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Draft for Community, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Event Evaluation for Presenters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Executive Directors Job Description, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Executive Director Search Committees - RESTRICTED, 1996; 1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Exempt Organization Certification, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Executive Personnel Policy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Financial Records (1 of 2), 1975-2007; Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Financial Records (2 of 2), 1975-2007; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fiscal Scholarship-Capital Pride Singers, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Five Year Plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Friend of the Council-Fundraising, 1980; 1982; 1988; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Forms and Graphics, 1980; 1985; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Funding Partnerships, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Fundraising 101-LGBTQ, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Garden Level Wheelchair Access Project, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Gay and Lesbian Young Adults-Request for Funding, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Gay Groups, Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Grant Proposals, 1996-1997; 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Historic Resources Commission, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - History of the Community Center, 1982; 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Holding Our Own-Grant Contract, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Inclusivity and Diversity Statements, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Insurance Policies, 1995-2000; 2002; 2006 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Invitations, Response and Thank You Cards Templates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Job Description and Procedures-Treasurer, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - John Cross Papers, 1975-1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - List Policy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Logo Proposal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Meeting Attendance Roster, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Meeting Facilitation-The No Magic Method, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Meeting Minutes (1 of 4), 1975-1977; 1979; 1981; 1988-1992; 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Meeting Minutes (2 of 4), 1975-1977; 1979; 1981; 1988-1992; 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Meeting Minutes (3 of 4), 1975-1977; 1979; 1981; 1988-1992; 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes (4 of 4), 1975-1977; 1979; 1981; 1988-1992; 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Member Questionnaire, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Membership Forms, 1979-1981; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Membership Requirements and Rules, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memberships, 1981; 2004-2005; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mission Statement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Model of a Non-For-Profit Organization, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Myron W. Taylor-Beneficiary, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Name and Purpose, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New York labor Law and Poster Service, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Non-Profit Management Seminar Series, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Notes, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Organizational Forces, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Organizational Issues, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Organizational Overview, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Part Time Temporary Office Administrator, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Past Presidents, 1970-1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Paul L. Leyden-Money Request from Fundraiser - RESTRICTED, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Peer Support Group-Policy and Procedure Manual, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Platform Lifts Renovations, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Policies and Procedures, 1999; 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Policy on Building Use, 1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Policy on Ticket Sales, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Planned Gift Management Fee Schedules, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Procedures for Managing AIDs Council of Northeastern New York, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Program Plans, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Program Planning Guide, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Programming Report, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Proposal-United Airlines INC and the Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, 1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Proposed Anti-Discrimination Policy, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Proposed Bidding Policies, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Proposed Policy on Center Behavioral Guidelines, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Proposed Six Month Business Plan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Rainbow Care, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Rainbow Care Staff, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Rebranding, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Resumes - RESTRICTED, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sample Development Plan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Smoking Policy, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Staffers Guide, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Staffers Records (1 of 2), 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Staffers Records (2 of 2), 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Strategic Plans, 2008-2010; 2012 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Stairway to the Stairs-Spring 1982 Roof Endowment (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Lease Agreement Between Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council, INC and Empire State Pride Agenda, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Subscriptions, 1984; 1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Survey, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Telephone Log Books (1 of 3), 1978; 1982-1984; 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Telephone Log Books (2 of 3), 1978; 1982-1984; 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Telephone Log Books (3 of 3), 1978; 1982-1984; 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer-Standing Operating Procedure, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Protection Act, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Volunteer Team, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Events, 1973-2017; 3.5 cubic ft.